Guide to the Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina Oral History Collection, 1981-2014 RL.11031
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Durham and surrounding areas, 1981; 1986-2008; 2014; undated; 3
  - Dworsky, Leon, 1985-1987; 42
    - Leon Dworsky. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff? for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, circa 1986-1987; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-155, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_155_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_155_002.wav)
      Container label: "Side A - Ezrahi, Side B- Katz - Dworsky"
    - Leon Dworsky. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project., 1987 January 5; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-026, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file RL11031_cs_026_001.wav, Audio-file RL11031_cs_026_002.wav)
      Container label: "Dworsky & Meyers"
    - Leon Dworsky. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project., 1987 January 5; transcript (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Dworsky, Phyllis, 1986; 43
    - Phyllis Dworsky. Interviewed by Rabbi Steven Sager and Beth-El Confirmation class, 1986 March 25; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-123)
  - Eliel, Ernest (Chapel Hill), 1986; 44
    - Ernest Eliel. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 December 11; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-048)
      Container label: "Eliel Shimm"
    - Ernest Eliel. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 December 11; transcript (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Evans, Eli, 1986; circa 2008; 45
    - Eli Evans. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 March 9; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-049, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_049_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_049_002.wav)
      Container label: "Eli Evans"
    - Eli Evans. Interviewed by Steven Channing for "Durham: a self-portrait" (documentary film) and Down Home project, circa 2008; digital betacam, 2 of 2 (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-028)
      Container label: "Eli Evans, Monroe Evans, Mrs. Monroe Evans"
    - Eli Evans. Interviewed by Steven Channing for "Durham: a self-portrait" (documentary film) and Down Home project, circa 2008; transcript (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Transcript label: "Eli Evans, outdoors interview"
    - Eli Evans. Interviewed by Steven Channing for "Durham: a self-portrait" (documentary film) and Down Home project, circa 2008; transcript (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Transcript label: "Eli Evans, formal interview"
  - Evans, Emanuel J., 1986; 46
    - Emanuel J. "Mutt" and Sara Evans. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 February 5; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-047, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_047_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_047_002.wav)
      Container label: "E.J. Evans"
    - Emanuel J. "Mutt" and Sara Evans. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 February 5; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Evans, Sara, 1986; 47
    - Emanuel J. "Mutt" and Sara Evans. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 February 5; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-047, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_047_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_047_002.wav)
    - Emanuel J. "Mutt" and Sara Evans. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 February 5; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Sara Evans. Interviewed by Rabbi Steven Sager and Beth-El Confirmation class, 1986 March 25; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-109)
      Container label: "Mrs. Sarah Evans"
  - Everett, Robinson O., 1992; 48
    - Robinson O. Everett. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 August 30; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-035)
      Container label: "Robinson O. Everett"
    - Robinson O. Everett. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 August 30; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Fein, Ruth and Rashi (Chapel Hill), 1994; 49
    - Ruth and Rashi Fein. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1994 April 10; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-124)
      Container label: "Ruth & Rashi Fein, Rabbi"
  - Fink, Sam and Jeanette, 1986; 50
    - Sam and Jeanette Fink. Interviewed by Debbie Wahl for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 4; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-125)
      Container label: "Interview with Sam & Jeanette Fink, May 4, 1986, by D. Wahl"
    - Sam and Jeanette Fink. Interviewed by Debbie Wahl for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 4; index (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Fox, Stan (Oxford), 2006; 51
    - Stan Fox. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 July 20; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-008)
      Container label: "Stan Fox, b-roll Stan at his desk"
    - Stan Fox. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 July 20; transcript (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Freedman, Molly, 1986; 52
    - Molly Freedman. Interviewed by Naomi Kirshner for Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class project, 1986 April 1; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-131)
      Container label: "Molly Freedman 4/1"
  - Ginsburg, Brenda, 1992; 53
    - Brenda Ginsburg. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 September 3; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-039)
      Container label: "Brenda Ginsburg"
    - Brenda Ginsburg. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 September 3; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Gladstein, Fanny, 1986; 54
    - Fanny Gladstein. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 February 5; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-140, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file RL11031-CS-140_001.wav)
      Container label: "Fanny Gladstein"
  - Gladstein, Melvin, circa 1986; 55
    - Melvin Gladstein. Interviewed for Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class project?, circa 1986; microcassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-MCS-003, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file RL11031-MCS-003_001.wav, Audio-file RL11031-MCS-003_002.wav)
      Container label: "Melvin Gladstein"
    - Melvin Gladstein. Interviewed for Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class project?, circa 1986; index (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Glustrom, Simon, Rabbi, 1992; 56
    - Rabbi Simon Glustrom. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 July 12; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Goldman, Lena, 2002; 2004; 57
    - Lena Goldman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 April; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-001)
      Container label: "Lena Goldman - 1"
    - Lena Goldman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 April; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-002)
      Container label: "Lena Goldman - 2"
    - Lena Goldman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 April; transcript (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Lena Goldman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2004; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-161)
      Container label: "Lena on deli's"
  - Goodman, Sadie, and Pat Silver, 1986; 58
    - Sadie Goodman and Pat Silver. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 January 29; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-139)
      Container label: "Sadie Goodman & Pat Silver"
    - Sadie Goodman and Pat Silver. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 January 29; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Sadie Goodman and Pat Silver. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 September; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-165, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_165_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_165_002.wav)
    - Sadie Goodman and Pat Silver. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 September; transcript (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Sadie Goodman and Pat Silver. Interviewed by Elyzse Lazarus and Lisa Lefstein for Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class project, 1986 April 1; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-147)
      Container label: "Sadie Goodman & Pat Silver; Elyse Lazarus, Lisa Lefstein"
    - Sadie Goodman and Pat Silver. Duplicate recording of interview by Elyzse Lazarus and Lisa Lefstein for Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class project, 1986 April 1; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-142)
      Container label: "Pat Silver"
  - Greenberg, Ruth (Chapel Hill), 1986; 59
    - Ruth Greenberg. Interviewed by Debbie Wahl for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 26; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-024)
      Container label: "Ruth Greenburg [Greenberg]"
    - Ruth Greenberg. Interviewed by Debbie Wahl for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 26; index (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Gross, Hudi and Samson, 1986; 60
    - Hudi and Samson Gross. Interviewed by Naomi Klein in Jerusalem, Israel for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 April 26; 30; transcript (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Grossman, Lynne, circa 2008
    - Lynne Grossman. Interviewed by Steven Channing for Durham: a self-portrait (documentary film) and Down Home project, circa 2008; digital betacam (Box 7, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-030)
      Container label: "Durham - Rogoff, Grossman"
  - Handler, Lucille, 1986; 61
    - Lucille Handler. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 September 25; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-043)
      Container label: "Lucy Handler"
    - Lucille Handler. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 September 25; transcript (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Hockfield, Joe, 1986; 62
    - Joe Hockfield. Interviewed by Ellie Meyer for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 10; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-133)
      Container label: "Joe Hockfield"
    - Joe Hockfield. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, circa 1986; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-138)
  - Jaffe, David, 1987; 63
    - David Jaffe. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project., 1987 September 10; transcript (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Experience in Durham and Chapel Hill: conversations with long-time residents, 1986; 64
    - Jewish Experience in Durham and Chapel Hill: conversations with long-time residents. Panel discussion moderated by Joel Schwartz, 1986 September 27; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-152)
      Participants include Henry Bane, Leon Dworsky, E. J. Evans, and Hazel Wishnov. Container label: "Old Time Residents/Jews in D[urham]"
    - Jewish Experience in Durham and Chapel Hill: conversations with long-time residents. Panel discussion moderated by Joel Schwartz, 1986 September 27; transcript (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Partial transcript and summary of discussion. Participants include Henry Bane, Leon Dworsky, E. J. Evans, and Hazel Wishnov."
  - Judea Reform Presidents, 1986; 65
    - Judea Reform Presidents. Interviewed by Sheldon Hanft and Leonard Rogoff, 1986 July 31; audiocassette, 1 of 3 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-151)
      Interviewees include Melvin Rashkis, Zora Rashkis, Judith Ruderman, Max Samfield, and Joel Smith. Container label: "Judea Reform Presidents - Max Samfield, Mel & Zora Rashkis, Judith Ruderman, Joel Smith"
    - Judea Reform Presidents. Interviewed by Sheldon Hanft and Leonard Rogoff, 1986 July 31; audiocassette, 2 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-021)
      Interviewees include Melvin Rashkis, Zora Rashkis, Judith Ruderman, Max Samfield, and Joel Smith. Container label: "Judea Reform Presidents"
    - Judea Reform Presidents. Interviewed by Sheldon Hanft and Leonard Rogoff, 1986 July 31; audiocassette, 3 of 3 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-111)
      Interviewees include Rabbi John Friedman and Rabbi Efraim Rosenzweig. Container label: "Friedman-Rosenzweig"
  - Julian, Milton (Chapel Hill), 1986; 66
    - Milton Julian. Interviewed by Judith L. Marks for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 27; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-136)
      Container label: "Milton Julian"
    - Milton Julian. Interviewed by Judith L. Marks for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 27; index (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Kaplan, Alfreda and Jake, 1986; 67
    - Alfreda and Jake Kaplan. Interviewed by Judith Ruderman for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 April 23; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-028)
      Container label: "Interview with Alfreda Kaplan on April 23, 1986. Also with Jake Kaplan. Interviewer Judith Ruderman, about 1 hr. 15 min."
    - Alfreda and Jake Kaplan. Interviewed by Judith Ruderman for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 April 23; index (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Katz, Gilbert "Gibby", 1986; 68
    - Gilbert "Gibby" Katz. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 January 25; audiocassette, 1 of 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-104, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_104_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_104_002.wav)
      Container label: "Gibby Katz Tape 1"
    - Gilbert "Gibby" Katz. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 January 25; audiocassette, 2 of 2 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-149)
      Container label: "Gilbert Katz Second Tape"
    - Gilbert "Gibby" Katz. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 January 25; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Gilbert "Gibby" Katz. Interviewed by Rabbi Steven Sager and Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class, circa 1986; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-103, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_103_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_103_002.wav)
      Container label: "Gibby Katz I"
    - Gilbert "Gibby" Katz. Interviewed by Rabbi Steven Sager and Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class, circa 1986; transcript (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Gilbert "Gibby" Katz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 August 1; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Gilbert "Gibby" Katz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 September 23; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-102)
      Container label: "Gibby Katz, 9/23/86, Chapel Hill, by Leonard Rogoff"
    - Gilbert "Gibby" Katz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 September 23; transcript (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Gilbert "Gibby" Katz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff? for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, circa 1986; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-155, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_155_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_155_002.wav)
  - Levin, Charlotte, 1986; 69
    - Charlotte Levin. Interviewed by Lori Posner for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 April 1; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-078)
      Container label: "Charlotte Levin"
    - Charlotte Levin. Interviewed by Lori Posner for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 April 1; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-087)
    - Charlotte Levin. Interviewed by Lori Posner for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 April 1; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Levitt, William Haskell (Chapel Hill), 1991; 70
    - William Haskell Levitt. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1991 December 12; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lewin, George and Ricki, 1986; 71
    - George and Ricki Lewin. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 January 29; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-019)
      Container label: "George & Ricky Lewin"
    - George and Ricki Lewin. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 January 29; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lieberman, Max, circa 1986; 72
    - Max Lieberman. Interviewed by David Zeiger and Nathan Siegel for Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class project, circa 1986; audiocassette, 1 of 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-088)
      Container label: "Max Lieberman/David Zeiger/Nathan Siegel"
    - Max Lieberman. Interviewed by David Zeiger and Nathan Siegel for Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class project, circa 1986; audiocassette, 2 of 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-096)
      Appears to be duplicate recording. Container label: "Max Lieberman "
    - Max Lieberman. Interviewed by David Zeiger and Nathan Siegel for Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class project, circa 1986; notes (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - London, Edith, 1986; 73
    - Edith London. Interviewed by J.J. Blum for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 22; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-095)
      Container label: "Interview with Edith London, May 22, 86"
    - Edith London. Interviewed by J.J. Blum for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 22; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Macklin, Harry and Sybil (Chapel Hill), 1986; 74
    - Harry and Sybil Macklin. Interviewed by Herbert Posner for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 July 4; transcript (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Marcus, Robert (Chapel Hill), circa 2014; 75
    - Robert Marcus. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff (commissioned by Shapell Foundation), circa 2014; audiocassette, 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-032)
      Container label: "Robert Marcus"
    - Robert Marcus. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff (commissioned by Shapell Foundation), circa 2014; audiocassette, 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-033)
  - Margolis, Norman and Mark, 1992; 76
    - Norman and Mark Margolis. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 April 30; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Margolis, Sam, 1985-1986; 77
    - Sam Margolis. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1985 November 15; audiocassette, 1 of 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-107, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_107_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_107_002.wav)
      Container label: "Sam Margolis"
    - Sam Margolis. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1985 November 15; audiocassette, 2 of 2 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-105, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_105_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_105_002.wav)
      Container label: "Sam Margolis 11/15"
    - Sam Margolis. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1985 November 15; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Sam Margolis. Interviewed by Robert Klein and Karen Feldman for Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class project, 1986? March 25; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-106, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_106_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_106_002.wav)
      Container label: "Sam Margolis 3/25; Robert Klein/Karen Feldman"
  - Markham, Charlie, 1986; 78
    - Charlie Markham. Interviewed by Robin Gruber for Duke University oral history seminar, 1986 January 23; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-097)
      Container label: "Charlie Markham"
  - Marks, Arthur (Chapel Hill), 1992; 79
    - Arthur Marks. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 April 21; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Meyer, Sigmund, 1986; 80
    - Sigmund Meyer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 September 25; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-012)
      Container label: "Sigmund Meyer "
    - Sigmund Meyer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 September 25; transcript (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Sigmund Meyer. Interviewed by Rabbi Steven Sager and Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class, circa 1986; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-001)
      Container label: "Sigmund Meyer/Rabbi Steve Sager"
    - Sigmund Meyer. Interviewed by Rabbi Steven Sager and Beth El Synagogue Confirmation class, circa 1986; transcript (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Sigmund Meyer. Interviewed by unknown interviewer, circa 1986; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-034)
  - Meyers, Eric, 1987; 81
    - Eric Meyers. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project., 1987 January 5; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-026, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_026_001.wav, Audio-file rl11031_cs_026_002.wav)
    - Eric Meyers. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project., 1987 January 5; transcript (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Morrison, Pearl, 1986; 82
    - Pearl Morrison. Interviewed by Ruth Greenberg for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 15; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-024)
      Container label: "Pearl Morrison"
    - Pearl Morrison. Interviewed by Ruth Greenberg for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1986 May 15; index (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Mowshowitz, Israel, Rabbi, 1987; 83
    - Rabbi Israel Mowshowitz. Self-interview for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1987 March; audiocassette, 1 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-014, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file RL11031_cs_014_001.wav)
      Container label: "Rabbi Israel Mowshowitz"
    - Rabbi Israel Mowshowitz. Self-interview for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1987 March; audiocassette, 2 of 2 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-017, Digital-materials RL11031-SET-0001, Audio-file rl11031_cs_017_001.wav)
    - Rabbi Israel Mowshowitz. Self-interview for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1987 March; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Patterson, Dan (Chapel Hill), 1992; 84
    - Dan Patterson. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1992 April 13; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Paul, Max, 2007; 85
    - Max Paul. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff, 2007; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-005)
      Container label: "Paul Max"
  - Pinsky, Mark, 1987; 86
    - Mark Pinsky. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1987 May 17; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-008)
      Container label: "Mark Pinsky"
    - Mark Pinsky. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Jewish community of Durham-Chapel Hill oral history project, 1987 May 17; transcript (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Rapoport, Amnon (Chapel Hill), 1987; 87
    - Amnon Rapoport. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1987 April 18; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-091)
      Container label: "Amnon Rapport [Rapoport]"
    - Amnon Rapoport. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Homelands project, 1987 April 18; transcript (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Rapport, Leonard (Durham / Chapel Hill / Asheville), 1987; 88